

PROFILE

Energetic, dedicated, and organized engineering student with experience in service, IT, and communication. Background in web editing and a passion for project management and web development. Skilled in independent work but also excels in collaborative efforts. Curious and committed to personal and professional development, as well as striving to enhance my skills.

LANGUAGES

Danish: FluentEnglish: AdvancedGerman: Conversational

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- I have worked with Java, PHP,
 HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python.
- I have also worked relational databases like PostgreSQL and NoSQL databases such as MongoDB.
- I am familiar with Docker and Kubernetes.
- I have worked with Git and Devops, including CI/CD practices.
- I am well-versed in the Microsoft Office suite, especially Word and Excel.

INTERESTS

- IT and programming
- Frontend web development
- Design
- Cooking and nutrition
- Fitness
- Nature and outdoor activities

FREJA MARIE MADSEN

CONTACT INFORMATION

PHONE NUMBER: 21854409 MAIL: frejamadsen1408@gamil.com

EDUCATION

NYMARKSKOLEN

August 2007 - June 2017 Completed primary school.

NYBORG GYMNASIUM HHX

August 2017 - June 2020

Completed HHX education. Majors: Business Economics A and Marketing A. Additionally, German A as a fifth major subject. Average Grade: 10.9

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN DENMARK - SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

September 2021 - June 2024

Currently on the $5^{\rm th}$ semester and planning to pursue a master's degree afterward.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CHOIR SINGER IN KØLSTRUP

June 2012 - July 2014

Responsibilities: Actively participated in singing lessons and performed at church services, weddings, and other events.

ASSISTANT COACH FOR U7 HANDBALL TEAM - VOLUNTEER WORK

August 2015 - January 2016

Responsibilities: Assisted with equipment and exercises.

SERVICE EMPLOYEE - PIZZA PRONTO

June 2015 - May 2016

Responsibilities: Assisted customers both in the restaurant and over the phone, maintained the restaurant area, and performed cleaning duties.

SERVICE EMPLOYEE - KERTEMINDE MINIGOLF GRILL AND ICE CREAM PARLOR

June 2016 - September 2022

Responsibilities: Customer service, food handling, store cleaning, responsibility for opening and closing the store, self-monitoring, and training new employees.

TEMPORARY WORKER - JKS

February 2021 - March 2021

Worked with damage service for Midtfyns Totalservice through JKS.

TEMPORARY WORKER - MOMENT

March 2021 - April 2021

Worked as a packaging employee at a By Growers nursery through Moment.

STUDENT HELPER - DEPARTMENT OF BIOLOGY AT SDU

September 2021 - Not completed

Responsibilities: Editing and maintaining the departments websites using Sitecore and Siteimprove.

VOLUNTEER AT SEMESTER START PARTY AT SDU

September 2022

Responsibilities: Drink production and stock replenishment.

STUDENT HELPER - THE CRM GROUP AT SDU IT

May 2023 - Not completed

Responsibilities: Helping users with problems and assisting the CRM group.